Five dollars and 29 cents?
They've got to be kidding.
Uh... Ahem.
Uh... Excuse me.
Excuse me. Excuse me.
Surely you've got something smaller.
- Sorry.
I bet they charge half this much
down at the Pharmacy Mart.
Oh, I know they do. I
shop there all the time.
Well, how come you
charge so much here?
Sir, you're not
buying just bandages.
You're buying
convenience, free parking,
our charm and good looks.
Don't move.
Hands up, both of you.
Lie down on the floor. Now!
Open that thing. Hurry up!
Lie down. Do it!
All right. Just stay
put, both of you.
Don't even think about moving
till I'm long gone. You hear?
I'm watching you.
You just stay put.
Y4J7.
Lucky guess, that's all it was.
Lucky for you, unlucky for my client.
Aw, come on, Dave.
Be a good sport.
The robber was
wearing a ski mask.
That lineup was a
joke and you know it.
Maybe I didn't see his face, but I
got a good look at everything else.
- His shoes and everything.
- And his car.
Somebody stole my client's car
and used it to commit the crime.
- Happens every day.
- Save it for the jury, Dave.
You think because you're Ben
Matlock, the jury's gonna lap up
whatever you put
in front of them.
- Lap that up, Dave.
- Hey, Ben. Ben.
Oh, go ahead. Touch me
and I'll get you for assault.
Jerk.
Takes one to know one.
Let's see now.
You'd like us to issue
a stop-work order
on a Jacuzzi that's being
built in Mr. Ramsey's backyard?
That's right. He's my
next-door neighbor,
and he's building that thing
less than 15 feet from my house.
The noise of the motor
by itself would be awful,
to say nothing of all
those half-naked people
that'll be jumping in
and out of it and yelling.
He's just mad because it's so close
to his fence, he won't be able to peep.
Peep? I'll have you know,
sir, I'm a church-going person.
You gray-haired old man.
- I'll gray-hair you.
- Gentlemen.
None of my other neighbors are
complaining about what I'm doing.
The neighbors moved away.
- Mr. Matlock, please.
- Sir.
He's in violation of the
property-line setback
clearly delineated in
the deed to his property.
Here's the...
See, I have a right.
It states that no one in
our neighborhood may build
within 5 feet of his or her
property lines without a variance,
and I'm not about
to give it to him.
Uh, Mr. Matlock, this isn't
the deed to his property.
It's the deed to Jimmy
Carter's home in Plains.
Did you put that in there?
How was I supposed
to put that in there?
How dare you?
Oh. Uh, um... Heh.
I'm Cliff Lewis. I'm
Mr. Matlock's associate.
Oh, yeah. Um... Uh... Heh.
We're obviously having a
little bit of a problem here.
Um, how about if I faxed you a copy of
that deed by the end of the afternoon?
Very well.
This case will be continued
till 9 a.m. tomorrow.
Next case.
You're nuttier than a
fruitcake. You know that?
- Are you sure you had the deed?
- Yeah, I put it in here this morning.
I don't walk around with the deed to
Jimmy Carter's house in my briefcase.
All right, I'll take care of the fax.
You go home and take a shower.
No.
Didn't you tell me you had a surprise
party for Judge Cooksey tonight?
Oh, that's right. And
you'll send the fax?
Yeah, I'll take care...
Yeah, I'll take care of it.
Well, Mr. Matlock,
good to see you again.
Nice to see you.
My, aren't we all
decked out this evening.
- What's the occasion?
- Judge Cooksey's party.
- Whose party? MATLOCK:
Richard Cooksey.
Surprise birthday party.
Invitation said, uh, black tie.
MAîTRE D': Uh, you're
sure the party's here?
Sure.
In the Fountain
Room, 7:30 tonight.
I'm afraid there's been some
kind of misunderstanding.
I RSVP'd and everything.
MAîTRE D': Yes, but
there's no party here tonight.
I left a message.
Well, perhaps you should
check your invitation.
I didn't make a mistake.
Mr. Matlock, the Bourne wedding
party is in the Fountain Room tonight.
Well, where's Judge
Cooksey's party?
Not here.
Right there.
See? Somebody's trying to
make me look like a jackass.
- It's him.
- Who's him?
Dave Burton.
That lawyer that's representing that
guy that robbed that convenience store.
He's trying to make me look nuts
so he can discredit me as a witness.
First at the hearing
and then at this party.
Ben, this invitation was mailed
two days before the robbery.
- No.
- Yeah, look at the postmark.
And how could he have
switched the deeds?
Hello?
WOMAN: You have a nice day?
- I know I did.
- Who's this?
That's for me to know
and you to never find out.
If you thought today was
fun, just wait till tomorrow.
Who is this?
Who was that?
It wasn't Dave Burton.
Who else got one of these?
I don't know. I
didn't ask anybody.
- It was supposed to be a secret.
- Good morning.
- Hey, Cliff.
Hey, Conrad, did Ben
tell you what happened?
Yeah. Somebody should check out
this phone number, don't you think?
Well, I did.
It's a voice-mail number for,
uh, some insurance company.
- What'd they say?
- They said, "That explains it."
- Explains what?
- The message they got two weeks ago
from some guy who said
that he'd be at the party
but wasn't thrilled about
having to rent a tux.
They just figured that
it was a wrong number.
I was the only one that called?
My feeling is, you were the
only one who got an invitation.
Somebody means business.
Well, we know it's a woman.
Mm. Probably Dave Burton.
He got his secretary
or some friend to call.
Or maybe it's somebody
with an ax to grind,
maybe on the back of your neck.
- That's no way to talk.
- Hey, I'm sorry.
Ax to grind on the
back of my neck.
Who? CONRAD: Joanna Wilton.
Early last month, she
was paroled from prison.
Who's Joanna Wilton?
She was George Wilton's
wife. He was a contractor.
She was having an affair with her
personal trainer, Harry Slade. Heh.
- Oh, he was something, huh? Heh.
- Heh.
- What do you mean? What?
- Ha, ha.
At the same time he was having
an affair with Joanna Wilton,
he was having an affair
with George Wilton's mistress.
Yeah, but remember, it was the other
woman he was having an affair with
that caused all the problems.
Oh, Harry, you've wrecked me.
The first woman was
George Wilton's wife, Joanna.
Sorry I didn't get a chance
to, you know, work you out.
Mm, that's all right.
I feel very tuned up.
Mwah.
- Where are you going?
- Oh, baby, it's late.
- Here.
- Oh. What is this?
Go ahead, open it.
Tropic of Capricorn,
Henry Miller. Whoa.
Read the inscription.
Oh. Joanna.
How can I thank you?
The second woman
Harry was seeing
was George Wilton's
mistress, Bridget.
Harry. What are you doing here?
Oh. Bridget, I need to talk.
Talk? You?
Bridget, please?
Okay, come on.
"Harry, you're the
best. Love, Joanna."
What the hell?
Joanna, what is this?
- What?
- Who's Harry?
Your personal trainer.
- George, your blood pressure...
- In our bed?!
George went over
to confront Harry
and found one big surprise.
Men didn't come this morning.
- Well, they forgot.
- Forgot?
Look, I'm building a
shopping center in Somerville.
Soon as I can spare a couple of
guys, I'll send them to your house.
My easy chair got
soaked last night.
I've been sitting in it for
years. It fits my body like skin.
It's irreplaceable. What
are you gonna do about it?
I didn't call you down here to talk
about your roof or your easy chair.
I called you down here because I'm
being charged with first-degree murder.
And I want you to defend me.
I'm willing to pay you twice your fee.
Yes?
What the hell are
you doing here?
George? I'm here trying to find
out about the women in Harry's life.
What the hell are
you doing here?
You're supposed to be
climbing my roof, not her.
Well, I was...
Did you say "the
women in Harry's life"?
Bridget.
George, listen to me.
Harry was a long time ago.
Pack up your stuff
and get out of here.
- George... GEORGE:
And leave the jewelry.
- Hold it. GEORGE:
You heard me. Get out.
- Hold it!
- What?!
She's not going
anywhere, you are.
And not a word
of this to anybody.
- I own this house. She's out.
- Are you out of your mind?
If one word gets out about Harry
having an affair with your wife
and your mistress,
the DA will kill us, fast.
Mom, uh, this is Miss Thomas.
She's one of George's attorneys.
I have a few questions,
if you don't mind.
Ten and...
Bobbie.
I wanna hear this.
Bobbie's from my first marriage.
When you have kids young,
you can't lie about your age.
It drives me crazy.
I imagine.
You told the police Harry
got to the house at 10:15.
The guesthouse, yeah.
Oh. Um...
Why the guesthouse?
Miss Thomas? Where
else would I entertain Harry?
Um, Harry left his
house around 9.
Did he say what
took him so long?
No.
And I didn't waste time asking.
I suppose you have an alibi
for the time of the murder.
No. I don't need one.
I didn't kill Harry.
This is kind of hard.
I mean, uh, this is a secret.
Secrets have a way of
coming out in a murder trial.
Well, that's what
I'm afraid of. Uh...
It's about where Harry was for
an hour before he saw my mom.
Yeah?
He was with me.
He was with you?
Boy, this guy must
have been truly amazing.
Ben finally pieced
the case together
two days after falling off a ladder
trying to fix the roof of his house.
The night before the murder, uh,
you, I guess you could
say, oh, uh, rendezvoused
with Harry out there in
the guesthouse, didn't you?
That's true.
And you'd been doing
that in the guesthouse
for four or five months, hadn't you?
- Yes.
But you never met with him
in the main house, did you?
Never. I'm not a tacky
woman, Mr. Matlock.
Uh, defense enters Exhibit H.
Would you examine
this and tell us what it is?
It's a gold cigarette
lighter I gave to Harry.
Your husband
found this, didn't he,
and discovered
your affair with Harry?
- Yes.
- Where'd he find it?
Um, in our bedroom.
I thought you said you never
met him in the main house.
- I guess I was mistaken.
- Uh-huh.
Harry was an hour late
meeting you that night, wasn't he?
Yes.
Who else was in
the house at the time
who could have been
in the master bedroom?
I don't know.
Your daughter, Bobbie, was
at home that night, wasn't she?
I don't remember.
I can subpoena
Bobbie's testimony.
No. No, Bobbie...
Bobbie was in the house.
- Yeah.
- That's right.
And Harry's lighter having
shown up in the master bedroom,
you knew he was
with Bobbie, didn't you?
It make you mad?
Very. I'm her mother.
Didn't it make you so angry
that you suddenly saw this whole
sordid mess as an opportunity
to get out of the marriage
and keep the money?
Isn't that why you shot Harry
Slade and framed your husband?
This is all ridiculous.
You can't prove any of
the things that you're saying.
For the record, and for you,
this officer...
Thank you... is
handing me a book.
I'm handing you the
same book for identification.
Now, examine that.
Tropic of Capricorn
by Henry Miller.
That's the same book
you gave Harry, isn't it?
Let the record show that this
officer, pursuant to a search warrant,
retrieved this book from
the courthouse parking lot.
It was found in the
locked trunk of a car
belonging to Mrs. Joanna Wilton.
I dated three girls at
the same time once.
- Yeah?
- Three girls?
Find out what that woman's been
doing since she got out of prison.
- Okay.
- Good.
Hello?
WOMAN: Hope you slept well
because you got a
big day ahead of you.
Better check the front door.
Wait. Who is...?
- Was that her? What did she say?
- I think so.
That's okay. You
look great there.
That's really nice.
- Ha-ha-ha.
- That's not me.
Are you sure? Because a
lot of guys your age would kill
to have a nice tight
little hind end like that.
That's not funny.
That's not my hind end.
- Ha-ha-ha.
- This is serious. This could ruin me.
CNN's on the phone.
They wanna know what number
sunscreen you were using.
- Ha-ha-ha.
- That's not funny!
It's not me. You've
got no right to print that.
Freedom of the press. It's all
there in the Fifth Amendment.
First Amendment.
The people have a right to know
what you public figures are really like.
All right, that's it.
Ben. Ben. You don't wanna see
this man with his pants down, do you?
- God, no.
- Then let me see the original picture.
Okay, okay. Keep your pants on.
Thank you. Oh.
It's your face on
someone else's body.
Where'd you get that?
I never reveal my sources.
I have my principles.
- I'll give you principles. Come on.
- Ben, Ben. No, Ben.
Okay, okay. I
got it in the mail.
Anonymous. No note. No
return address. Nothing.
Hey, give that back. That
picture's private property.
So sue me.
Anybody home? MATLOCK: Yeah.
Got the lowdown on Joanna
Wilton. Who wants to hear about it?
Me.
What's all this?
We're trying to figure out
where his head came from.
- I've wondered that.
- Ha, ha. No, in the fake photo.
Okay, I just talked to Bobbie.
Joanna's daughter, remember?
When Joanna was paroled,
Bobbie picked her up
and took her home
and everything was fine.
Then a couple of days later,
out of the blue, she went wacko.
Three weeks ago, they put her under
lock and key in a hospital in Valdosta.
Well, guess it isn't her.
Ooh, wait a second.
Do you remember what was there?
I think there was a picture there
that was taken in a courtroom.
I don't know, Ben.
Someone sneaks in here,
they mess with your
briefcase, they steal a photo.
You gotta start
locking your doors.
I do, when I think of it.
Any idea what river this is?
I have a travel-agent friend who
swears that this is Canyon Springs.
It's a place right
outside of Austin, Texas.
Texas?
Lorraine Ortega.
Well, now, who's
Lorraine Ortega?
Well, that's her alias. Her
real name is Cissy Lockwood.
I gotta make a phone call.
Cissy Lockwood was this
bartender at this honky-tonk
where a friend of mine named
Anne Johnson used to work.
Anne had this kid whose name was
Jimmy who was real good at drawing,
and he invented this comic-book
hero he called Mr. Awesome.
Come on, honey.
Anne had just broken up with
her boyfriend, Dwayne Meeks.
Don't I get a say
in any of this?
There is nothing between
us, Dwayne, and you know it.
Oh, I think there is.
And it ain't over until I say
it's over, you understand?
I don't think you're getting that part.
- Let go of her!
Get off me, you
little... Let go of me.
Jimmy, stand back. Stay away
from us, Dwayne. I mean it.
Do it, Mom. Get him.
Baby, what are you
gonna do with that?
Dwayne.
- Come here, come here. Come on.
- Just leave me alone.
- Aah!
- Hey.
Anne's friend Walt was
always there to help her.
Come on.
Waste him, Walt, waste him.
Now, apologize to the lady.
- I said, apologize.
- Aah! All right, all right.
I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
You pick up your stuff tomorrow
or it'll be out on the street.
And don't you ever lay a
hand on me or my son again.
The next day, Dwayne went to
Anne's place to pick up his stuff.
What the...?
Anne was arrested, and
I got Ben to defend her.
Why is it every time
I get a little time off
to do a few things around the
house like change a few light bulbs,
somebody I know
has a friend in trouble?
Ben, you gotta defend her.
She is such a nice person.
You say she's a waitress?
Well, it's the only
job she could get.
I mean, you know, the tips.
And she's got this little boy.
Well, how about
a public defender?
Ben, you've gotta defend her.
You'll see, Anne Johnson
is one of the nicest,
most hard-working, honest, and
courageous people I've ever met.
Well, hell, Conrad,
instead of defending her,
why don't I just nominate
her for president?
Lorraine Ortega was one
of Dwayne's old girlfriends.
Who is your good-looking friend?
Excuse me. You left your hat.
Oh. Uh, I'm Ben
Matlock, Anne's lawyer.
You gonna be
able to get her off?
I hope so.
Dwayne had it
coming, that's for sure.
I hear you used to,
uh, go out with him.
Me and half the women here.
Went through us one by one.
The big stud servicing his herd.
Oh. How did you take that?
No skin off my hide.
I wasn't his first and Anne
wouldn't have been his last.
Had this sort of
feeling about Jimmy.
What?
I went to his school and
I talked to his principal.
Yeah?
He wasn't in class
the day of the murder.
Hello, Jimmy.
Hi, Mr. Matlock.
- I'll meet you guys downstairs.
- Okay.
So, um, ahem, how was school?
- Fine.
- Mm-hm.
I found the stun gun.
What'd you do with it?
I took it to the police.
Why'd you do that?
What if they find
fingerprints or something?
Whose fingerprints are you afraid
they'll find on it, Jimmy? Yours?
No.
Who are you protecting, Jimmy?
- Jimmy?
- I don't wanna talk anymore.
Well...
You think I killed him?
Well, you had that fight
with him the night before.
If I wanted to kill him, I'd have
done it right then and there.
I certainly wouldn't
try to frame Annie for it.
Oh, well, maybe you
didn't mean to frame Anne.
Maybe you didn't
mean to kill Dwayne.
Maybe you just wanted to have it out
with him and things went a little too far.
Maybe you had the stun gun and
were gonna give it back to Anne
and used it on Dwayne
without even thinking.
That's a bunch of bull.
You sure can draw,
you got an eye for detail.
- I just draw what's there.
- Yeah.
You know when you drew these?
I always put the
date on the back.
Miss Ortega, did you know
the deceased, Dwayne Meeks?
Everybody at Vern's knew him.
- You went out with him.
- For a while, yeah.
We broke up. MATLOCK: When?
About a month before he died.
Oh. Did you, uh...?
Did you live with him?
- No.
- No?
What about all these
checks you wrote to him?
See, here's one for 700,
and here's one for 300,
and here's one for
500, and there's more.
He... They were loans.
Loans?
But he...
They weren't loans, were they?
They were blackmail
payments, weren't they?
Why would Dwayne
be blackmailing me?
Because he found
out who you really are.
Not Lorraine Ortega
from Memphis, Tennessee,
but Cissy Lockwood
from Amarillo, Texas.
And what does
that have to do...?
He also found out that
there's an outstanding warrant
for your arrest back in Texas.
You fell in with a pretty bad
dude about four years ago,
and the two of you
robbed a gas station.
Nearly killed the attendant.
- And you drove the car to get away.
- I did not.
That's what the fella told the
police when they caught up to him.
- He's lying.
- Nevertheless, you're a fugitive.
I imagine that's why
you changed your name
when you moved here to Atlanta.
And why you gave
Dwayne all that money,
so he wouldn't
tell the authorities.
But when you realized the payments
were never gonna stop, you killed him.
None of that is true.
Would you please tell the
judge and the court what this is?
It's a belt buckle.
Not just any belt buckle.
This is the belt
buckle they gave you
when you were voted American
Barrel Racing Champion in 1987. Right?
Yes. MATLOCK: Yeah.
The police found it in your apartment
this morning, with a warrant, of course,
and the reason I subpoenaed it
was because of these drawings
done by Jimmy Johnson.
See? Now, here's...
Here's a picture of
you wearing the belt.
See there? This is in July.
Before you started going
with Dwayne. See there?
Now, these two
are pictures of Dwayne
wearing the belt buckle
just before you broke
up with him. See there?
Yet the police found it in
your possession this morning.
- How could that be?
- I won that belt buckle
because I used to be
the best at something.
I'd have never given it to
somebody like Dwayne ever.
Then why was he wearing
it when he was killed?
You took it off him, didn't you?
After you killed him.
Because, like you say, this belt
buckle means more to you than anything.
And you weren't about to
see him with it for all eternity.
Were you?
Spoke to Bob Brooks.
Cissy Lockwood was
paroled two months ago,
and she's working not five miles
from here at the CanCan Dry Cleaners.
- Thank you.
- Okay.
So you mean Ben Matlock
doesn't really run around naked
every chance he gets?
- No, the photograph was a fake.
- Could have fooled me.
Cissy, where were you the day
before yesterday around 8 a.m.?
Where do you think I was?
Well, I think you were
trespassing in Ben's house,
getting back at him
for putting you in prison.
Well, for your information,
I was in San Antonio
helping my daddy
celebrate his retirement.
Got back yesterday afternoon.
Besides that, I don't hold
anything against Ben Matlock.
He was just doing his job.
Fixed that fuel line for
you, Cissy. Runs like a top.
Thank you, Josh. You are a doll.
Everything okay here?
Oh, yeah. Conrad
and me's old friends.
Stop by next time
you're out this way.
Yeah, I will.
She really was in San Antonio?
- Yeah, she was there.
- And you checked?
Yes.
- You know who else is out on parole?
- Who?
That model you used to date.
Carla? MATLOCK: Mm.
Ooh, Carla Royce.
Carla Royce. Carla Royce.
Yeah. Carla Royce was this
woman that I met in New York,
gorgeous, that I was nuts about.
She came to Atlanta for a
shoot, so I went to watch her work.
And this photographer she
was posing for... Harry Samuels?
Yeah... was having
real problems.
Now, get back in there
and do exactly as you're told,
or you're fired. You got that?
What?
I hear you've been bad-mouthing me.
- Jackie.
Spengler's is not
interested in using my people
for their Christmas catalog.
I hear you're the reason why.
All I told them is they
could stay under budget
if they used less
expensive models.
You told their art
director that my models
tend to be under-accomplished
and overpriced!
Wait, wait, they
misunderstood me.
Please don't do that!
I don't like it when people
talk behind my back!
If you've got something to
say, then say it to my face!
Jackie, please calm down.
You have crossed
over the line, Harry.
This is war.
And believe me,
when the dust clears,
there's only going to
be one of us standing.
And it isn't going to be you.
Jackie Whitman was the biggest
agent in the modeling business,
and she could destroy Harry.
All right, lunch. Be back at 3.
That's some argument old
Harry had with that lady, huh?
That lady is my
agent, Jackie Whitman.
Poor Harry. He really blew it.
She can really keep
him from getting work?
You bet.
That'll be the last major
spread he does for a long time.
Hi, Harry.
I called to see if you wanted
any lunch. Where you been?
Wild-goose chase.
What do you mean,
wild-goose chase?
Just what I said.
Harry, you been here long?
I just got in. Why?
I got good news and bad news.
The good news is Jackie Whitman's
not gonna bother you anymore.
Well, what's up?
Carla's agent, Jackie Whitman
was murdered this afternoon.
I heard that on the news.
Your agent. I'm sorry.
They arrested my
friend, Harry Samuels.
- Oh.
- I've known Harry for years.
He's impulsive and
he's temperamental,
but he's not a murderer.
Oh.
His answering service got a
message from somebody named Jackie
asking him to meet her at
the park so they could talk.
He went to the park
and no one was there.
And when he got back to
the studio, he found her dead.
Think somebody set him up?
- Yeah.
He can pay your fee, Ben.
The next day, Ben found
out something about Carla
that flipped me out.
Oh, yeah, here, take a look.
Oh, here, use this.
Ooh.
Boy, that Lauren is
a beauty, isn't she?
- So's Carla.
- Oh, yeah.
Look at Carla's smile and
poise. She's a born model.
I know. So was her sister.
- Sister?
- Mm-hm.
Her name was Monica. Whew,
we're talking major good looks.
Once she and Carla started
working, they never stopped.
Only Monica couldn't
handle the life.
Drugs?
Oh, yeah, in a big way. Whew.
She dropped out
about a year ago,
and the next thing we
heard, she was dead.
It was a, um, car
accident or something.
And then Carla stopped working
for a month or two after that.
When she came back, she was
really determined, almost driven.
She hasn't stopped since.
Monica. Who was her agent?
Same as Carla's. Jackie Whitman.
How long have you been a
fashion model, Miss Royce?
About four years.
Your sister, Monica, started modeling
about that same time, didn't she?
- That's right. MATLOCK:
What happened to her?
She died in a car
accident almost a year ago.
Hmm.
Who was her agent?
Jackie Whitman.
Your sister, Monica, was arrested once
for possession of cocaine, wasn't she?
- What's my sister got to do with this?
- Please answer the question.
Yes, she was arrested.
- Was she prosecuted?
- No.
How come?
The charges were dropped.
The charges were dropped?
That would be very
difficult to get done.
Who got the charges dropped?
Jackie Whitman. MATLOCK: Oh.
So Jackie Whitman knew
your sister had a drug problem.
Yes.
Did she ever suggest that
Monica go for treatment?
No.
Did you ever suggest
that she get treatment?
I begged her. I pleaded.
I even threatened her. I...
She had more control
over your sister than you did,
and you hated her for it.
When Jackie walked
into that darkroom,
you stabbed her to death
with those scissors, didn't you?
Absolutely not!
The proof is in the acid burn
that's on your lower left arm.
I don't know what
you're talking about.
I'm talking about the burn you sustained
when you stabbed Jackie Whitman.
She fell against the counter,
knocked over a bottle of acid,
and part of it splashed
on your arm, didn't it?
- No.
- That's why
during the rest of the shoot,
you took great pains to hide
your left arm from the camera.
I have a burn on my arm, yes.
But it's from spilling
hot coffee on it, not acid.
That's an acid burn.
You know it, and I know it,
and this police
report proves it.
A lot of bottles of makeup
got broken that afternoon
during the argument between
Harry and Jackie, didn't they?
The place was a mess.
Harry's assistant, Frannie
Morrissey, cleaned it up.
Also, she replaced all of the
old makeup bottles with new ones.
Now, that means
the only fingerprints that
should be on those bottles
when the police
dusted after the murder
were hers.
Would you please
look at this police report
and read the names of the
people whose prints were found
on one of those bottles?
"Frances Morrissey and..."
"Carla Royce."
That's you.
How did your fingerprints get all
over one of those brand-new bottles?
I'll check on Carla.
Holy. Look at the time.
Oh, Lord.
I guess he took all the
money out of the drawer
and then he told us
to get down on the floor
and stay there till he was gone.
But when I heard him start up
his car, I looked up as he drove off
and I saw his license
plate, CUY4J7.
The same plate which,
as was stipulated,
was issued last
July to the defendant.
Nothing further, Your Honor.
Mr. Burton.
We all couldn't help but notice that
you arrived a little late, Mr. Matlock.
Everything all right?
- Everything's fine.
- You sure?
I hear you had a little problem with
the planning commission the other day.
You brought the
wrong papers with you?
Objection. Irrelevant.
Goes to credibility, Your Honor.
I'll allow it.
Rumor has it that you recently
showed up at Chez Munroe
for a party that didn't
exist. That right?
Yeah, but the reason for that...
Is this you, Mr. Matlock?
No.
Well, who is it? Your evil twin?
That's my head, but not
my hind end. Ask anybody.
- Anybody?
- Well, no, not anybody.
- That's not my hind end.
- Mr. Matlock. Language.
- Rear end.
- Language.
Tush. Give me a break.
Your Honor.
You may proceed, Mr. Burton.
Mr. Matlock, do you really expect
these good people to believe
that somebody as flamboyant
as you obviously are
can say for certain it was my client,
whose face you admit you never saw,
was without a doubt the person
who robbed that convenience store?
I picked him out of a lineup. I
heard his voice. I saw his shoes.
- You saw his shoes?
- Yeah.
What did his shoes look like?
They were running shoes,
black, with purple and pink trim.
What brand were they?
- I don't know.
- Well, then.
Perhaps this will
refresh your memory.
So which shoe was it?
This one?
Or maybe it was this one.
I can't say.
- Can't you even try?
- I'd be guessing.
- You'd be guessing?
Just like you did when you
picked my client out of that lineup.
- Right, Mr. Matlock?
- No.
Nothing further.
- Gonna be at home?
- No.
I'm gonna stay and see
what the jury has to say.
What if they find
that guy not guilty?
I don't know. Then... Then
they find him not guilty.
I'll look like a jackass. Hmm.
Has the jury reached a verdict?
We have, Your Honor.
We find the defendant
guilty as charged.
The defendant will
return to this courtroom
at 9:00 on the 23rd of
this month for sentencing.
Court is adjourned.
They believed you after all.
Congratulations, Ben, you
pulled another one out of the fire.
Carla's in France?
Maybe it is Dave Burton.
Well, I haven't gotten
any phone calls for a while.
So let's forget it and
have a nice bowl of chili.
Oh, no, no, no.
I don't think so.
Um, no, I have a lunch
meeting tomorrow,
and those onions you
use are really lethal.
Good night.
What about you, Conrad?
I'd better not. I got a
date in two days. No.
I really hated prison.
- Oh. Cissy.
- Only thing that kept me going
was thinking about all the things I
was gonna do to you once I got out.
Thought you were in San Antonio.
My boyfriend, Josh,
he's real handy with locks.
Oh, you're the one that's
been messing with my papers
and sending me
to the wrong parties
and publishing that phony
picture of my hind end.
And now you're gonna kill me?
Bingo.
I really hadn't
planned to kill you,
I just wanted to
make you suffer.
Wreck your life bit
by bit, day by day.
But when I watched
that trial today
and saw how you got everybody
around here brainwashed
into thinking you're God's gift
to truth and justice, I got mad.
I said to myself,
"To hell with it.
Give him what he deserves
and get it over with."
No, no, no.
Cissy, you don't... You don't...
You don't have to kill me, Cissy.
I mean, you're out.
You're out of prison now, and
you got this nice new boyfriend,
and you could keep
playing nasty tricks on me.
No!
Well, wait a minute.
- What are you doing?
- I'm praying.
If I'm gonna go see Jesus, I
want him to know I'm coming.
I thought I heard you.
Yeah. Recognized
your motorcycle.
Took me a minute, but I finally
figured out where I'd seen it before.
Next time, try parking three
blocks to the south, Cissy.
- Thanks.
- It's okay.
Wanna call the police?
What's happening? I
saw Conrad make a U-turn.
Uh-huh. Hello, Cliff.
This is Cissy Lockwood.
I sent her to prison
a few years ago,
and she stopped by
to say everything's fine
and there's no hard feelings.
And to have a
nice bowl of chili.
www.tvsubtitles.net